
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:" If a shirt is originally priced at $80 and is discounted by 20%, what will be the sale price?",
    answer: "$64",
    options: [
      "$64",
      "$78",
      "$72",
      "$82"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " A trader bought a watch for $120 and sold it for $150. What is the profit percentage?",
    answer: "25%",
    options: [
      "20%",
      "25%",
      "30%",
      " 35%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " If the ratio of boys to girls in a class is 3:2 and there are 15 boys, how many girls are there?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If 6 workers can complete a task in 8 days, how many workers are needed to complete the same task in 4 days?",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "16",
      "12",
      "25",
      "2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " If a student scored 75 out of 100 in an exam, what is the percentage scored?",
    answer: "75%",
    options: [
      "65%",
      "75%",
      "85%",
      "80%"
    ]
  },
  

     {
   numb: 6,
   question: " A shopkeeper sells a shirt at a loss of 10%. If the cost price is $200, what is the selling price?",
    answer: "$180",
    options: [
      "$180",
      "$190",
      "$197",
      "$300"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "If the ratio of the ages of two people is 3:5 and the sum of their ages is 64, find their ages.",
     answer: "12,20",
     options: [
       "12,20",
       "15,30",
       "16,11",
       "18,40"
     ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "A machine can produce 100 items in 5 hours. How many machines are needed to produce 500 items in 2 hours?",
       answer:"6",
       options: [
         "4" ,
         "5",
         "6",
         "7"
       ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: " A price of a book is increased by 15%. If the original price was $50, what is the new price?",
         answer: "$60",
         options: [
           "$60",
           "$51",
           "$52",
           "$57"
         ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
          question: "A shopkeeper sells a pen at a profit of 25%. If the selling price is $12.50, what is the cost price?",
           answer: "$9.00",
           options: [
             "$8.00",
             "$2.00",
             "$7.00",
             "$9.00"
           ]
          }
];